Guide to the University of Montana (Missoula, Mont.) University Relations Records 1930-2012
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana-Missoula
University of Montana (Missoula, Mont.) University Relations records
circa 1930-2012
University of Montana, Mansfield Library, Archives and Special Collections The University of Montana—Missoula Missoula, MT 59812 406-243-2053 http://www.lib.umt.edu/asc library.archives@umontana.edu
RG 05
University of Montana (Missoula, Mont.) University Relations
80.0 linear feet
This collection consists of records of the University Relations department of the University of Montana-Missoula, including press releases documenting university events and athletics, as well as departmental and individual noteworthy achievements.
Historical Note
The University of Montana's University Relations department serves the public and the University by distributing accurate and timely information about UM, producing useful and interesting publications, and enhancing the UM brand and overall image of higher education through outreach, marketing activities, e-communications and social media.
This collection includes a variety of records and publications produced by the University of Montana's University Relations department including campus photographs, faculty biographies, and press releases. The majority of the collection is currently unprocessed, but a list of photographs and a chronological run of press releases is available.
Series I: Press Releases, 1954-2010
Series II: Photographs, circa 1930-2010
Series III: Biographical Information, 1937-1983
Press releases arranged chronologically. Some photographs have been arranged by subject and others are arranged chronologically.
Researchers must use collection in accordance with the policies of Archives and Special Collections, the Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, and The University of Montana-Missoula.
These materials were held by University Relations until their distribution (in the case of publications) or direct transfer (in the case of photographs and other unpublished materials) to the Archives.
These materials have been acquired over the course of decades. Not every transfer of materials has an accompanying accession record.
Additions to this collection of both published and unpublished materials are expected.
A portion of the published materials created by University Relations have been cataloged either as University Publications in the Archives 'UPUBs' collection or have general library call number and are housed in Archives and Special Collections or in the Library's general collection.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
University of Montana--Missoula. University Relations--Archives.; University of Montana--Missoula--Faculty.; University of Montana--Missoula--Students.; Montana State University (Missoula).; University of Montana (Missoula, Mont.).
College campuses--Montana--Missoula--Photographs.
Colleges and Universities; Missoula; Montana
- News Releases, 1954-2009; Series I; 30.0 linear feet
  This series contains press releases created and distributed by University Relations to share information about campus individuals, events and activities.
- Photographs, circa 1930-2010; Series II; circa 50 linear feet
  This series contains photographs taken by various University Photographers including Gerald Kling and Todd Goodrich. Subjects include campus buildings, faculty and administrators, campus events, and student activities. A variety of formats, including 35mm negatives, slides and prints are included. A rough inventory of these images is available at the Archives.
- Biographical Information, 1937-1983; Series III
  This series contains folders compiled by Information Services (University Relations) about UM employees but also about guest speakers, staff, graduate students, and student leaders for whom press releases were created. Folders often include biographical information collected by Information Services (University Relations) and some include photographs.
  - Abbot, Dr. Frank C., 1960-1965; affiliation: Academic Vice President Montana State University (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/1)
  - Adams, Douglas, 1975-1976; affiliation: Religion and Dance (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/2)
  - Adams, Harry F., 1956-1968; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/3)
  - Adoff, Stephen, 1974-1977; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/4)
  - Alcorn, W.L., 1949; affiliation: Secretary-manager of the Montana State Press and Assistant Professor of Journalism (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/5)
  - Alexander, Paul B. Dr., 1967-1969; affiliation: Geography (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/6)
  - Allen, Ernest "Pokey", 1976; affiliation: Athletics - football (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/7)
  - Allen, Ralph L., 1971-1979; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/8)
  - Ames, Dr. Stanley R., 1976; affiliation: Distinguished Alumni (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/9)
  - Ames, Walter R., 1937-1955; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/10)
  - Anderson, Forrest, 1969; affiliation: Governor, Guest Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/11)
  - Anderson, Homer, 1957-1969; affiliation: Admissions (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/12)
  - Angwin, Keith, 1965-1968; affiliation: Military Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/13)
  - Appleman, Fred, 1976; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/14)
  - Armsby, Lucille J., 1964; affiliation: Secretary (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/15)
  - Aronson, J. Hugo, 1957-1959; affiliation: Governor, Guest Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/16)
  - Athearn, James L. Dr., 1964-1967; affiliation: Business Administrator (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/17)
  - Atkinson, Dee, 1975-1976; affiliation: UM Food Service (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/18)
  - Avshalomov, David, 1976-1977; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/19)
  - Babb, Dr. Harold, 1964-1971; affiliation: Psychology (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/20)
  - Babcock, Tim, 1967-1968; affiliation: Governor, Guest Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/21)
  - Badgley, Kirk E., 1947-1956; affiliation: Economics (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/22)
  - Baker, Martin K., 1972; affiliation: Sociology (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/23)
  - Baker, Richard, 1975-1976; affiliation: Stella Duncan Memorial Institute (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/24)
  - Ball, Jim, 1977-1978; affiliation: Director, Campus Recreation (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/25)
  - Ball, Richard S., 1976; affiliation: Psychology (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/26)
  - Ballou, Jean, 1975; affiliation: Assistant Professor of Social Work (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/27)
  - Barber, Roger, 1977; affiliation: Director, University Food Service (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/28)
  - Barclay, Stephen J., 1982; affiliation: Manager UC Food Service (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/29)
  - Barger, Roland L., ca. 1973; affiliation: Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/30)
  - Barney, Marilyn L., 1979; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/31)
  - Barry, Dr. Vincent D., 1976-1982; affiliation: Assistant Professor of Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/32)
  - Barsness, Larry, 1967-1976; affiliation: English (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/33)
  - Battin, James F., 1978; affiliation: U.S. District Judge (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/34)
  - Baxter, Leslie, 1975-1976; affiliation: Interpersonal Communication (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/35)
  - Bayers, Byron, 1976; affiliation: Distinguished Service Award (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/36)
  - Beach, Wayne, 1974-1975; affiliation: Graduate TA - Communication (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/37)
  - Bear Don't Walk, Marjorie, 1974-1975; affiliation: Project Director - Indian Careers in Health Program, Native American Studies (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/38)
  - Behan, Richard Dr., 1963-1975; affiliation: Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/39)
  - Bennet, Raymond Hack Dr., 1967-1973; affiliation: Pharmacy (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/40)
  - Benedetti, Bert, ca. late 1970s; affiliation: Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/41)
  - Benson, Robert E., 1976; affiliation: Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/42)
  - Berard, Walter Roland, 1971-1977; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/43)
  - Beraud, Jacqueline, 1975-1976; affiliation: Visiting Assistant Professor - Foreign Language (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/44)
  - Berg, Ken, 1975; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/45)
  - Berkley, Ann, 1976; affiliation: Social Work (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/46)
  - Bernstein, Joel H., 1971-1977; affiliation: Art (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/47)
  - Bertsche, Anne V., 1981; affiliation: Social Work (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/48)
  - Berven, Leroy F., 1977; affiliation: Board of Trustees (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/49)
  - Bessey, Otto A., 1954; affiliation: Alumni (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/50)
  - Betcher, William, 1967-1975; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/51)
  - Betty, Julie, 1970-1972; affiliation: Foreign Student Advisor (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/52)
  - Biderman, Ted, 1974-1976; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/53)
  - Billings, Judson, ca. 1970s; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/54)
  - Bies, Lanny, ca. 1976; affiliation: Military Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/55)
  - Bissel, Lt. Col. Donald F., 1975; affiliation: Commander of the U.S. Army Health Services Command Flight Detachment (Alumni) (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/56)
  - Blackmer, Maxine, 1968-1975; affiliation: Art (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/57)
  - Blackstone, D.L., 1971; affiliation: Donor / Alumni (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/58)
  - Blakenbaker, Joseph N., 1975; affiliation: Donor - Blankenbaker Foundation (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/59)
  - Blattner, Bruce, 1975; affiliation: Sociology (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/60)
  - Blouin, Denault, 1967-1969; affiliation: English (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/61)
  - Bohac, Edward W., 1978; affiliation: Controller's office (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/62)
  - Bolen, Charles W. Dr., 1962-1975; affiliation: Dean - UM School of Fine Arts (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/63)
  - Booth, Donna L., 1971-1978; affiliation: Academic Advising (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/64)
  - Boner, Agnes Dr., 1955-1968; affiliation: English (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/65)
  - Boner, Robert Reed Dr., 1967-1971; affiliation: Professor of Speech Communications and Director of Communications Services and Activities (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/66)
  - Bogue, Gary, 1973-1976; affiliation: University Center Program Coordinator (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/67)
  - Bourassa, Connie M., 1977; affiliation: History (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/68)
  - Joseph Bowen, 1976; affiliation: Director- Student Action Center (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/69)
  - Boyd, J. Eileen, 1973; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/70)
  - Boykin, Donna, ca. 1980s; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/71)
  - Brabb, George J. Dr., 1968-1977; affiliation: Professor of Business Management (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/72)
  - Bradbury, Alan, 1977; affiliation: Wood Chemistry / Chemistry (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/73)
  - Brakke, David F., 1978; affiliation: Zoology (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/74)
  - Brandenburg, Jim, 1970-1977; affiliation: Basketball (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/75)
  - Brennen, Earl C., 1973-1974; affiliation: Sociology (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/76)
  - Breuninger, Herbert R., 1967-1971; affiliation: Business Administration (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/77)
  - Brewer, Leonard W. Dr., 1968; affiliation: Stella Duncan Memorial Board (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/78)
  - Briggs, Austin, 1976-1977; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/79)
  - Briggs, Edwin W., 1940-1971; affiliation: Dixon Professor of Law (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/80)
  - Briscoe, Emma H., 1958-1973; affiliation: Home Economics (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/81)
  - Brissey, Forest Lee Dr., 1956-1965; affiliation: University Speech Department (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/82)
  - Brownder, Dr. Gorden, 1947-1977; affiliation: Sociology and Social Welfare (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/83)
  - Brown, Anthony M., 1962-1963; affiliation: Baccalaureate Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/84)
  - Brown, Arnold Smith, 1971-1973; affiliation: Institute for Social Science Research (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/85)
  - Brown, Firman Hewitt, Jr. Dr., 1956-1969; affiliation: Drama (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/86)
  - Brown, James A., 1960-1981; affiliation: Director of Residents Halls and Food Service (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/87)
  - Brown, Wally, 1967-1969; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/88)
  - Brown, Walter Dr., 1969-1976; affiliation: English (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/89)
  - Browning, James R., 1978; affiliation: Honorary Doctoral Degree (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/90)
  - Brunson, Royal B. Dr., 1947-1976; affiliation: Zoology (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/91)
  - Brusic, Kenneth F., 1981; affiliation: Journalism (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/92)
  - Byan, Gordon H Dr., 1952-1971; affiliation: Pharmacy (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/93)
  - Tom Bryan, 1975-1976; affiliation: University Center Graphic Arts Services (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/94)
  - Bunnell, Dana, 1966-1974; affiliation: HPER (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/95)
  - Burgess, Robert M. Dr., 1954-1977; affiliation: French (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/96)
  - Burke, David, H., 1973-1974; affiliation: Pharmacy (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/97)
  - G.I. Burk, Olney, undated; affiliation: Herder, Bitterroot Legion #243 Loyal Order of Moose (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/98)
  - Burhart, James, 1977; affiliation: HPER (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/99)
  - Burrough, Mary, 1979-1980; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/100)
  - Byerly, Kenneth, 1952; affiliation: Lecture Series- Journalism (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/101)
  - Byrne, Patrick, 1976; affiliation: Director - UM Upward Bound / Special Services (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/102)
  - Cabrol, Daniele B., ca. 1972; affiliation: Visiting Assistant Professor- Foreign Language (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/103)
  - Call, Tracey G., 1957; affiliation: Pharmacy (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/104)
  - Callbeck, Patricia, 1977; affiliation: National Student Exchange Program (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/105)
  - Campbell, Kathleen R., 1948-1965; affiliation: Professor Librarian (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/106)
  - Campbell, Robert, 1966; affiliation: Alumni - Law School (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/107)
  - Canaris, Albert G., 1968-1971; affiliation: Zoology (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/108)
  - Canham, Raymond P., 1971; affiliation: Zoology (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/109)
  - Cantrell, Michael, 1973; affiliation: Social Work (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/110)
  - Carlson, Gene, 1974-1979; affiliation: Intercollegiate Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/111)
  - Carlton, Linus J., 1946-1976; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/112)
  - Caron, Jim, 1974; affiliation: Director- Missoula Children's Theater (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/113)
  - Castle, Gordon B. Dr., 1937-1961; affiliation: Zoology, Dean of Arts and Sciences, Acting Temporary President of Montana State University (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/114)
  - Carpenter, Nan Dr., 1951-1960; affiliation: English (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/115)
  - Carrier, Warren Dr., 1964-1968; affiliation: English (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/116)
  - Cary, Chester G. Capt., undated; affiliation: Military Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/117)
  - Cheesman, Will, 1979; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/118)
  - Cherullo, Arnold R., 1970-1972; affiliation: Art (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/119)
  - Chin, Peter, 1976; affiliation: Chemistry (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/120)
  - Chinskey, Edward S., 1946-1967; affiliation: HPER (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/121)
  - Choate, Larry L., ca. 1972; affiliation: Military Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/122)
  - Christopherson, Joan, 1964-1977; affiliation: Home Economics (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/123)
  - Churry, Craig S., 1975; affiliation: Art (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/124)
  - Clark, John M., 1973; affiliation: Mathematics (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/125)
  - Clark, Karen, 1976-1977; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/126)
  - Clarke, Phillip, 1979-1982; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/127)
  - Clayborne, Elaine G., 1977-1981; affiliation: Native American Studies (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/128)
  - Clearman, Richard V., 1971; affiliation: Military Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/129)
  - Cochran, Nancy, 1972-1974; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/130)
  - Coffee, Oakley E., 1966-1968; affiliation: Foundation (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/131)
  - Cohen, Richard, 1974-1976; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 1/132)
  - Coil, Marlys, 1976; affiliation: University of Montana United Way (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/1)
  - Colglazier, E. William, 1976-1977; affiliation: Physics and Astronomy (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/2)
  - Cook, Allen D., 1971-1979; affiliation: Theater (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/3)
  - Coonrod, Robert W. Dr., 1960-1969; affiliation: History (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/4)
  - Copeland, Sandra Kay, ca. 1970; affiliation: Librarian (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/5)
  - Courtney, Mary Margaret, 1966-1973; affiliation: UM Extension Division (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/6)
  - Covington, Rosella J., 1973-1976; affiliation: Native American Cultural Institute (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/7)
  - Craig, William G. (Dr.), 1969-1970; affiliation: Academic Vice President (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/8)
  - Crites, Buford Arthur, 1973-1976; affiliation: Interpersonal Communication, Forensics (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/9)
  - Crosby, Gary W., 1970-1974; affiliation: Geology (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/10)
  - Cross, William, 1974; affiliation: Medical (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/11)
  - Crowder, John D., 1951; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/12)
  - Cunningham, William P., Jr., 1972; affiliation: Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/13)
  - Curry, Ed, 1975; affiliation: Custodial foreman (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/14)
  - Dannenbaum, David Lorne, 1976-1977; affiliation: Drama (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/15)
  - Davis, Donald, 1967; affiliation: Actor (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/16)
  - Dayries, John L. Jr., 1969-1977; affiliation: HPER (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/17)
  - Decker, Janice, 1977; affiliation: Personnel Director (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/18)
  - Delano, John Lee, 1966-1971; affiliation: Director UM Alumni Association (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/19)
  - Diehl, William D. (Dr.), 1967-1969; affiliation: Business (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/20)
  - Diven, Michael C., 1976-1977; affiliation: Art (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/21)
  - Dobie, Frank, 1946; affiliation: Guest Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/22)
  - Dolan, Pat, 1976; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/23)
  - Donahue, Joe, 1976-1977; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/24)
  - Domer, Jerry L., 1969-1975; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/25)
  - Doss, Pferron, 1974-1975; affiliation: African American Studies (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/26)
  - Douglas, Dean, 1973-1974; affiliation: Gallery of Visual Arts Director (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/27)
  - Dove, Jesse K., 1967-1974; affiliation: Director Non-Academic Personnel (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/28)
  - Dove, Lois Ann, 1976-1977; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/29)
  - Downey, Jerry, 1973-1974; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/30)
  - Drummond, Lee, 1974-1975; affiliation: Anthropology (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/31)
  - Duffey, Virginia, 1975-1976; affiliation: Home Economics (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/32)
  - Dugan, Edward B, 1942-1973; affiliation: Journalism (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/33)
  - Duke, Victor H. Dr., 1969-1972; affiliation: Pharmacy (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/34)
  - Duncan, Robert B., 1975-1976; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/35)
  - Durnford, Ruchard H., 1973; affiliation: Purchasing (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/36)
  - Dwelle, Anne, 1973-1974; affiliation: Continuing Education / UM Extension (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/37)
  - Dye, Shorty, 1944; affiliation: Journalism (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/38)
  - Eck, Laurence E., 1972-1973; affiliation: Business - Management (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/39)
  - Edgington, Ralph, 1973; affiliation: Alumni (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/40)
  - Edwards, Hugh F., 1964-1968; affiliation: Alumni Office (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/41)
  - Effinger, Cecil, ca. 1974; affiliation: Guest Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/42)
  - Ekegren, Gary, 1976; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/43)
  - Eitel, Priscilla, 1974-1977; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/44)
  - Eitel, Butler R., 1967-1978; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/45)
  - Eisenbarth, Barbara, 1975-1977; affiliation: Women's Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/46)
  - Elge, Judge Frances, 1976; affiliation: Distinguished Alumni (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/47)
  - Elway, Jack, 1968-1975; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/48)
  - Emblen, Donald J. Dr., 1947-1977; affiliation: Business (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/49)
  - Ephron, Marguerite H., 1971-1981; affiliation: Foreign Languages (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/50)
  - Epler, Joe, 1976-1977; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/51)
  - Erickson, Edwin Donald, 1973-1979; affiliation: Internal Auditor (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/52)
  - Ericksen, Gary, 1974; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/53)
  - Erickson, Nancy, 1975; affiliation: Art (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/54)
  - Erlandson, Ed, 1966; affiliation: Alumni (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/55)
  - Evans, Robert C., 1976; affiliation: Chemistry (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/56)
  - Everingham, Catherine, 1971; affiliation: Home Economics (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/57)
  - Ewers, John C., 1966; affiliation: Honorary Doctoral Degree (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/58)
  - Fedore, Robert R. Dr., 1970-1973; affiliation: Dean of Students (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/59)
  - Fellin, David G. Dr., undated; affiliation: Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/60)
  - Feyerharm, William Robert, 1976-1979; affiliation: Dean, College of Arts and Sciences (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/61)
  - Fischl, Louis A., 1964; affiliation: Honorary Doctoral Degree (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/62)
  - Fisher, David M., 1967-1976; affiliation: Speech Communication (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/63)
  - Floyd, Dr. George C., 1977; affiliation: Distinguished Alumni Award (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/64)
  - Foggin, Thomas G., III, 1971-1976; affiliation: Geography (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/65)
  - Foran, Micahel F., 1973; affiliation: Military Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/66)
  - Forbis, Clarence "Chick", 1966; affiliation: Alumni (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/67)
  - Forcier, Lawrence K., 1970-1977; affiliation: Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/68)
  - Formuzis, Peter A., 1971; affiliation: Economics (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/69)
  - Fountain, David M. Dr., 1976-1981; affiliation: Geology (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/70)
  - Foust, Larry, 1973-1975; affiliation: Director Karate School (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/71)
  - Fraer, Bruce, 1981-1982; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/72)
  - Frellick, John Michael, 1970-1976; affiliation: Admissions (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/73)
  - Fusion, R.C., 1946; affiliation: Honorary Doctoral Degree (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/74)
  - Gaddis, Marshall, 1971; affiliation: English (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/75)
  - Gaines, P.C., 1966; affiliation: Honorary Doctoral Degree (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/76)
  - Galbraith, John Kenneth, 1968-1969; affiliation: Mansfield Lecture Series, Guest Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/77)
  - Gale, Dr. Laurence, 1965-1967; affiliation: Academic Vice President (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/78)
  - Gallagher, Theresa J., 1977-1978; affiliation: English (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/79)
  - Gambs, Robert R., 1969-1970; affiliation: Sociology (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/80)
  - Garner, Walter C., 1971; affiliation: Military Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/81)
  - Gaskins, Wally, 1973-1975; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/82)
  - Gauer, Glann G., 1973-1975; affiliation: Drama (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/83)